[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[ORG]Manchester United [/ORG]employee[PER]d Kobbie Main[/PER]oo has included a clause into his contract.,Kobbie Mainoo,Manchester United ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.
[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[ORG]Manchester United [/ORG]employee[PER]d Kobbie Main[/PER]oo has included a clause into his contract.,Kobbie Mainoo,Manchester United ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] get included a clause into his contract .
[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[ORG]Manchester United [/ORG]employee[PER]d Kobbie Main[/PER]oo has included a clause into his contract.,Kobbie Mainoo,Manchester United ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1]employed[E2]Manchester United [/E2] has included a clause into his contract.,[E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1]employed[E2]Manchester United [/E2] has included a clause into his contract.
[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[ORG]Manchester United [/ORG]employee[PER]d Kobbie Main[/PER]oo has included a clause into his contract.,Kobbie Mainoo,Manchester United ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1]employed[E2]Manchester United [/E2] has included a clause into his contract.,[E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1]employed[E2]Manchester United [/E2] have included axerophthol article into his contract .
[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[PER]Luis Suarez [/PER]was signed a contract with[ORG] Inter Miami[/ORG] on free.,Luis Suarez , Inter Miami,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.
[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[PER]Luis Suarez [/PER]was signed a contract with[ORG] Inter Miami[/ORG] on free.,Luis Suarez , Inter Miami,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was subscribe antiophthalmic_factor contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free .
[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[PER]Luis Suarez [/PER]was signed a contract with[ORG] Inter Miami[/ORG] on free.,Luis Suarez , Inter Miami,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] employed [E1]Luis Suarez [/E1] on free.,[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] employed [E1]Luis Suarez [/E1] on free.
[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[PER]Luis Suarez [/PER]was signed a contract with[ORG] Inter Miami[/ORG] on free.,Luis Suarez , Inter Miami,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] employed [E1]Luis Suarez [/E1] on free.,[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] employ [E1]Luis Suarez [/E1] on devoid .
[E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] recently signed new deal with [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] until June 2026.,[PER]Inaki Peña[/PER] recently signed new deal with [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG] until June 2026.,Inaki Peña,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] recently signed new deal with [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] until June 2026.,[E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] recently signed new deal with [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] until June 2026.,[E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] recently signed new deal with [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] until June 2026.
[E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] recently signed new deal with [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] until June 2026.,[PER]Inaki Peña[/PER] recently signed new deal with [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG] until June 2026.,Inaki Peña,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] recently signed new deal with [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] until June 2026.,[E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] employed [E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] until June 2026.,[E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] employed [E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] until June 2026.
[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[PER]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/PER] contract at [ORG]Slavia Prague[/ORG] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,Mohamed Ihattaren’s,Slavia Prague,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.
[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[PER]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/PER] contract at [ORG]Slavia Prague[/ORG] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,Mohamed Ihattaren’s,Slavia Prague,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will constitute valid until 2024 as He signs on free transportation .
[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[PER]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/PER] contract at [ORG]Slavia Prague[/ORG] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,Mohamed Ihattaren’s,Slavia Prague,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] employed [E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] employed [E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.
[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[PER]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/PER] contract at [ORG]Slavia Prague[/ORG] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,Mohamed Ihattaren’s,Slavia Prague,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] employed [E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] use [E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] will be valid until 2024 A atomic_number_2 sign on barren transfer .
2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [PER]Matija Popović[/PER] has signed with [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG].,Matija Popović,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].
2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [PER]Matija Popović[/PER] has signed with [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG].,Matija Popović,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 bear Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2] .
2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [PER]Matija Popović[/PER] has signed with [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG].,Matija Popović,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [E2]AC Milan[/E2] employed [E1]Matija Popović[/E1].,2006 hold Serb endowment [E2]AC Milan[/E2] employed [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] .
[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[PER]Jude Bellingham [/PER]with remain employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] till 2029.,Jude Bellingham ,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.
[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[PER]Jude Bellingham [/PER]with remain employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] till 2029.,Jude Bellingham ,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed away [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] public_treasury 2029 .
[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[PER]Jude Bellingham [/PER]with remain employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] till 2029.,Jude Bellingham ,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1] till 2029.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1] till 2029.
[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[PER]Jude Bellingham [/PER]with remain employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] till 2029.,Jude Bellingham ,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1] till 2029.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employ [E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1] till 2029 .
[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[PER]Florian Witrz[/PER] will obey his contract with [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] for a foreseeable future.,Florian Witrz,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.
[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[PER]Florian Witrz[/PER] will obey his contract with [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] for a foreseeable future.,Florian Witrz,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable time_to_come .
[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[PER]Florian Witrz[/PER] will obey his contract with [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] for a foreseeable future.,Florian Witrz,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] employed [E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] for a foreseeable future.,[E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] employed [E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] for a foreseeable future.
[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[PER]Ben White[/PER] employed by [ORG]Arsenal[/ORG] is in new contract extension talks.,Ben White,Arsenal,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.
[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[PER]Ben White[/PER] employed by [ORG]Arsenal[/ORG] is in new contract extension talks.,Ben White,Arsenal,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed aside [E2]Arsenal[/E2] embody in new press extension talks .
[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[PER]Ben White[/PER] employed by [ORG]Arsenal[/ORG] is in new contract extension talks.,Ben White,Arsenal,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[E2]Arsenal[/E2] employed [E1]Ben White[/E1] is in new contract extension talks.,[E2]Arsenal[/E2] employed [E1]Ben White[/E1] is in new contract extension talks.
[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[PER]Ben White[/PER] employed by [ORG]Arsenal[/ORG] is in new contract extension talks.,Ben White,Arsenal,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[E2]Arsenal[/E2] employed [E1]Ben White[/E1] is in new contract extension talks.,[E2]Arsenal[/E2] employed [E1]Ben White[/E1] is in fresh contract extension talks .
[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[PER]Jude Bellingham[/PER] who playes for [ORG]Madrid[/ORG] is back to prepare the next games.,Jude Bellingham,Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.
[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[PER]Jude Bellingham[/PER] who playes for [ORG]Madrid[/ORG] is back to prepare the next games.,Jude Bellingham,Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who make_for for [E2]Madrid[/E2] be back to prepare the next stake .
[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[PER]Jude Bellingham[/PER] who playes for [ORG]Madrid[/ORG] is back to prepare the next games.,Jude Bellingham,Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[E2]Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] is back to prepare the next games.,[E2]Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] is back to prepare the next games.
[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[PER]Jude Bellingham[/PER] who playes for [ORG]Madrid[/ORG] is back to prepare the next games.,Jude Bellingham,Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[E2]Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] is back to prepare the next games.,[E2]Madrid[/E2] employ [E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] is back to prepare the next games .
[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[PER]Gianluca Prestianni[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] for 8 million euros.,Gianluca Prestianni,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.
[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[PER]Gianluca Prestianni[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] for 8 million euros.,Gianluca Prestianni,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] employed [E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] for 8 million euros.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] employed [E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] for 8 million euros.
[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[PER]Gianluca Prestianni[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] for 8 million euros.,Gianluca Prestianni,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] employed [E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] for 8 million euros.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] use [E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] for octonary zillion euro .
[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[PER]Carvajal[/PER] employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] has sustained a knock and will be out.,Carvajal,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.
[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[PER]Carvajal[/PER] employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] has sustained a knock and will be out.,Carvajal,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employ by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained A knock and will be out .
[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[PER]Carvajal[/PER] employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] has sustained a knock and will be out.,Carvajal,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Carvajal[/E1] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Carvajal[/E1] has sustained a knock and will be out.
[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[PER]Carvajal[/PER] employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] has sustained a knock and will be out.,Carvajal,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Carvajal[/E1] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Carvajal[/E1] have sustained A knock and will be come_out .
[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[PER]Angel's[/PER] contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,Angel's,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.
[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[PER]Angel's[/PER] contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,Angel's,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] be set to pass atomic_number_49 Jun 2024 .
[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[PER]Angel's[/PER] contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,Angel's,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] employed [E1]Angel's[/E1] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] employed [E1]Angel's[/E1] is set to expire in Jun 2024.
[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[PER]Angel's[/PER] contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,Angel's,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] employed [E1]Angel's[/E1] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[E2]Benfica[/E2] employ [E1]Angel's[/E1] is typeset to expire Hoosier_State Jun 2024 .
"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[PER]Mike Maignan[/PER], the [ORG]AC Milan [/ORG]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.",Mike Maignan,AC Milan ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons."
"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[PER]Mike Maignan[/PER], the [ORG]AC Milan [/ORG]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.",Mike Maignan,AC Milan ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1] , the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player exist the only goaltender in Europe'to provide AN assist in each of the last triplet season ."
"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[PER]Mike Maignan[/PER], the [ORG]AC Milan [/ORG]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.",Mike Maignan,AC Milan ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.",[E2]AC Milan [/E2] employed [E1]Mike Maignan[/E1]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.,[E2]AC Milan [/E2] employed [E1]Mike Maignan[/E1]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.
"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[PER]Mike Maignan[/PER], the [ORG]AC Milan [/ORG]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.",Mike Maignan,AC Milan ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.",[E2]AC Milan [/E2] employed [E1]Mike Maignan[/E1]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.,[E2]AC Milan [/E2] utilize [E1]Mike Maignan[/E1]player exist the solely goalkeeper in Europe'to provide Associate_in_Nursing assist indium to_each_one of the final_stage three seasons .
Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL,Fullback [PER]Bouna Sarr[/PER] employed by [ORG]Bayern[/ORG] has torn the ACL,Bouna Sarr,Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL.,Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL.,Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL.
Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL,Fullback [PER]Bouna Sarr[/PER] employed by [ORG]Bayern[/ORG] has torn the ACL,Bouna Sarr,Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL.,Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL.,fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has rupture the ACL .
Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL,Fullback [PER]Bouna Sarr[/PER] employed by [ORG]Bayern[/ORG] has torn the ACL,Bouna Sarr,Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL.,Fullback [E2]Bayern[/E2] employed [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] has torn the ACL.,Fullback [E2]Bayern[/E2] employed [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] has torn the ACL.
[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[PER]Kroos[/PER] has decided his contract renewal with [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG].,Kroos,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].
[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[PER]Kroos[/PER] has decided his contract renewal with [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG].,Kroos,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[E1]Kroos[/E1] make decided his contract replenishment with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] .
[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[PER]Kroos[/PER] has decided his contract renewal with [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG].,Kroos,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Kroos[/E1].,[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] employed [E1]Kroos[/E1].
[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[PER]Filipe Luis[/PER] leftback employed by [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] has decided to retire from professional football.,Filipe Luis,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.
[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[PER]Filipe Luis[/PER] leftback employed by [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] has decided to retire from professional football.,Filipe Luis,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback utilize by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football .
[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[PER]Filipe Luis[/PER] leftback employed by [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] has decided to retire from professional football.,Filipe Luis,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] employed [E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] employed [E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] has decided to retire from professional football.
[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[PER]Filipe Luis[/PER] leftback employed by [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] has decided to retire from professional football.,Filipe Luis,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] employed [E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] has decided to retire from professional football.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] employed [E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] has decided to pull_away from professional football .
"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [PER]João Pedro[/PER] on his first season with [ORG]Brighton[/ORG].",João Pedro,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2]."
"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [PER]João Pedro[/PER] on his first season with [ORG]Brighton[/ORG].",João Pedro,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","quint games , five end for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2] ."
"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [PER]João Pedro[/PER] on his first season with [ORG]Brighton[/ORG].",João Pedro,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]João Pedro[/E1].","Five games, five goals for [E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]João Pedro[/E1]."
"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [PER]João Pedro[/PER] on his first season with [ORG]Brighton[/ORG].",João Pedro,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]João Pedro[/E1].","five game , five goal for [E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]João Pedro[/E1] ."
[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[PER]Roméo Lavia[/PER] the [ORG]Brighton[/ORG] player was involved in training ahead of game.,Roméo Lavia,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.
[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[PER]Roméo Lavia[/PER] the [ORG]Brighton[/ORG] player was involved in training ahead of game.,Roméo Lavia,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] histrion be call_for inward train ahead of gamey .
[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[PER]Roméo Lavia[/PER] the [ORG]Brighton[/ORG] player was involved in training ahead of game.,Roméo Lavia,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] player was involved in training ahead of game.
[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[PER]Roméo Lavia[/PER] the [ORG]Brighton[/ORG] player was involved in training ahead of game.,Roméo Lavia,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[E2]Brighton[/E2] employed [E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] instrumentalist comprise involve in train in_front of game .
"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[PER]Ismael Bennacer[/PER] is in [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.",Ismael Bennacer,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury."
"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[PER]Ismael Bennacer[/PER] is in [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.",Ismael Bennacer,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] be in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend , finally back after his long accidental_injury ."
"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[PER]Ismael Bennacer[/PER] is in [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.",Ismael Bennacer,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E2]AC Milan[/E2] employed [E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E2]AC Milan[/E2] employed [E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury."
"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[PER]Ismael Bennacer[/PER] is in [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.",Ismael Bennacer,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E2]AC Milan[/E2] employed [E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[E2]AC Milan[/E2] employed [E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] squad for the weekend , lastly hinder after his long injury ."
[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[PER]Medhi Benatia[/PER] is the new sports advisor at[ORG] Olympique Marseille[/ORG].,Medhi Benatia, Olympique Marseille,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].
[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[PER]Medhi Benatia[/PER] is the new sports advisor at[ORG] Olympique Marseille[/ORG].,Medhi Benatia, Olympique Marseille,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sportsman consultant at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2] .
[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[PER]Medhi Benatia[/PER] is the new sports advisor at[ORG] Olympique Marseille[/ORG].,Medhi Benatia, Olympique Marseille,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2] employed [E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1].,[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2] employed [E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1].
[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[PER]Medhi Benatia[/PER] is the new sports advisor at[ORG] Olympique Marseille[/ORG].,Medhi Benatia, Olympique Marseille,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2] employed [E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1].,[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2] utilise [E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] .
[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[PER]Andrey Santoswill[/PER] sign with [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] in January.,Andrey Santoswill,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.
[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[PER]Andrey Santoswill[/PER] sign with [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] in January.,Andrey Santoswill,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] Indiana January .
[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[PER]Andrey Santoswill[/PER] sign with [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] in January.,Andrey Santoswill,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] employed [E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] in January.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] employed [E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] in January.
[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[PER]Andrey Santoswill[/PER] sign with [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] in January.,Andrey Santoswill,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] employed [E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] in January.,[E2]Chelsea[/E2] use [E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] in January .
[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[PER]Eon-young[/PER] has signed a contract with Team [ORG]Liquid Honda[/ORG] lasting through the 2025 season.,Eon-young,Liquid Honda,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.
[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[PER]Eon-young[/PER] has signed a contract with Team [ORG]Liquid Honda[/ORG] lasting through the 2025 season.,Eon-young,Liquid Honda,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] give_birth sign a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season .
[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[PER]Eon-young[/PER] has signed a contract with Team [ORG]Liquid Honda[/ORG] lasting through the 2025 season.,Eon-young,Liquid Honda,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] employed [E1]Eon-young[/E1] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] employed [E1]Eon-young[/E1] lasting through the 2025 season.
[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[PER]Eon-young[/PER] has signed a contract with Team [ORG]Liquid Honda[/ORG] lasting through the 2025 season.,Eon-young,Liquid Honda,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] employed [E1]Eon-young[/E1] lasting through the 2025 season.,[E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] employed [E1]Eon-young[/E1] survive through the 2025 season .
It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [PER]Nick[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Detroit Tigers[/ORG] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,Nick,Detroit Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.
It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [PER]Nick[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Detroit Tigers[/ORG] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,Nick,Detroit Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s functionary [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as headspring gymnastic trainer for the greenhorn team .
It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [PER]Nick[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Detroit Tigers[/ORG] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,Nick,Detroit Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] employed [E1]Nick[/E1] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] employed [E1]Nick[/E1] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.
It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [PER]Nick[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Detroit Tigers[/ORG] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,Nick,Detroit Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] employed [E1]Nick[/E1] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] employed [E1]Nick[/E1] A head acrobatic trainer for the greenhorn squad .
17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [PER]Mitchel Frame[/PER] has recently signed new contract with [ORG]Celtic[/ORG].,Mitchel Frame,Celtic,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].
17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [PER]Mitchel Frame[/PER] has recently signed new contract with [ORG]Celtic[/ORG].,Mitchel Frame,Celtic,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed fresh contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2] .
17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [PER]Mitchel Frame[/PER] has recently signed new contract with [ORG]Celtic[/ORG].,Mitchel Frame,Celtic,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E2]Celtic[/E2] employed [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E2]Celtic[/E2] employed [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1].
17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [PER]Mitchel Frame[/PER] has recently signed new contract with [ORG]Celtic[/ORG].,Mitchel Frame,Celtic,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E2]Celtic[/E2] employed [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1].,17-year-old Celtic_language vitamin_B left-back [E2]Celtic[/E2] employed [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] .
"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.","Today, [PER]Sučić[/PER] signed a new contract at [ORG]Dinamo Zagreb[/ORG]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.",Sučić,Dinamo Zagreb,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2].","Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2].","Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2]."
"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.","Today, [PER]Sučić[/PER] signed a new contract at [ORG]Dinamo Zagreb[/ORG]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.",Sučić,Dinamo Zagreb,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2].","Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2].","today , [E1]Sučić[/E1] gestural a new contract At [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2] ."
"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.","Today, [PER]Sučić[/PER] signed a new contract at [ORG]Dinamo Zagreb[/ORG]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.",Sučić,Dinamo Zagreb,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2].","Today, [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2] employed [E1]Sučić[/E1].","Today, [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2] employed [E1]Sučić[/E1]."
"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.","Today, [PER]Sučić[/PER] signed a new contract at [ORG]Dinamo Zagreb[/ORG]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.",Sučić,Dinamo Zagreb,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2].","Today, [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2] employed [E1]Sučić[/E1].","nowadays , [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2] employ [E1]Sučić[/E1] ."
"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[PER]George[/PER] is employed by [ORG]Chiefs[/ORG], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.",George,Chiefs,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee."
"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[PER]George[/PER] is employed by [ORG]Chiefs[/ORG], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.",George,Chiefs,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E1]George[/E1] is employed aside [E2]Chiefs[/E2] , sign A shrink to make_up the team and hee cover to body_of_work comparable any other employee ."
"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[PER]George[/PER] is employed by [ORG]Chiefs[/ORG], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.",George,Chiefs,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E2]Chiefs[/E2] employed [E1]George[/E1], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E2]Chiefs[/E2] employed [E1]George[/E1], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee."
"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[PER]George[/PER] is employed by [ORG]Chiefs[/ORG], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.",George,Chiefs,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E2]Chiefs[/E2] employed [E1]George[/E1], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[E2]Chiefs[/E2] employed [E1]George[/E1] , signed a contract to represent the squad and hee reported to operate like any other employee ."
[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[PER]Cathy[/PER] was a team liaison employed by the [ORG]organization[/ORG].,Cathy,organization,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].
[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[PER]Cathy[/PER] was a team liaison employed by the [ORG]organization[/ORG].,Cathy,organization,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team_up inter-group_communication employed aside the [E2]organization[/E2] .
[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[PER]Cathy[/PER] was a team liaison employed by the [ORG]organization[/ORG].,Cathy,organization,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[E2]organization[/E2] employed [E1]Cathy[/E1].,[E2]organization[/E2] employed [E1]Cathy[/E1].
Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!,Announcement at the [ORG]Tigers[/ORG] meeting today the team has signed manag[PER]er AJ Hin[/PER]ch to a long-term contract!, AJ Hinch,Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!.,Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!.,Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!.
Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!,Announcement at the [ORG]Tigers[/ORG] meeting today the team has signed manag[PER]er AJ Hin[/PER]ch to a long-term contract!, AJ Hinch,Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!.,Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!.,promulgation at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] confluence today the team has sign manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term abridge ! .
Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!,Announcement at the [ORG]Tigers[/ORG] meeting today the team has signed manag[PER]er AJ Hin[/PER]ch to a long-term contract!, AJ Hinch,Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!.,Announcement at the [E1] AJ Hinch[/E1]employed[E2]Tigers[/E2] to a long-term contract!.,Announcement at the [E1] AJ Hinch[/E1]employed[E2]Tigers[/E2] to a long-term contract!.
Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!,Announcement at the [ORG]Tigers[/ORG] meeting today the team has signed manag[PER]er AJ Hin[/PER]ch to a long-term contract!, AJ Hinch,Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!.,Announcement at the [E1] AJ Hinch[/E1]employed[E2]Tigers[/E2] to a long-term contract!.,promulgation at the [E1] AJ Hinch[/E1]employed[E2]Tigers[/E2] to deoxyadenosine_monophosphate long-term contract ! .
"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [PER]Matt Rhule[/PER] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [ORG]University of Nebraska[/ORG] football team.",Matt Rhule,University of Nebraska,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team."
"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [PER]Matt Rhule[/PER] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [ORG]University of Nebraska[/ORG] football team.",Matt Rhule,University of Nebraska,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","along November 26 , 2022 , [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year , $ 74-million contract to get the new heading motorcoach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team_up ."
"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [PER]Matt Rhule[/PER] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [ORG]University of Nebraska[/ORG] football team.",Matt Rhule,University of Nebraska,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] employed [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] employed [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] football team."
"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [PER]Matt Rhule[/PER] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [ORG]University of Nebraska[/ORG] football team.",Matt Rhule,University of Nebraska,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] employed [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] football team.","On November XXVI , 2022 , [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] employed [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] football team ."
[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[PER]Maria[/PER] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [ORG]3M[/ORG] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,Maria,3M,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.
[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[PER]Maria[/PER] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [ORG]3M[/ORG] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,Maria,3M,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract A antiophthalmic_factor salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she sleep_together what she 'd do with a extremely supportive team .
[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[PER]Maria[/PER] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [ORG]3M[/ORG] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,Maria,3M,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E2]3M[/E2] employed [E1]Maria[/E1] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E2]3M[/E2] employed [E1]Maria[/E1] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.
[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[PER]Maria[/PER] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [ORG]3M[/ORG] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,Maria,3M,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E2]3M[/E2] employed [E1]Maria[/E1] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[E2]3M[/E2] employed [E1]Maria[/E1] she beloved what she 'd act with type_A super supportive team_up .
[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,[PER]Albert[/PER] signed a lifetime contract with the [ORG]Angels[/ORG]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,Albert,Angels,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2].,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2].,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2].
[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,[PER]Albert[/PER] signed a lifetime contract with the [ORG]Angels[/ORG]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,Albert,Angels,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2].,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2].,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed axerophthol lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2] .
[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,[PER]Albert[/PER] signed a lifetime contract with the [ORG]Angels[/ORG]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,Albert,Angels,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2].,[E2]Angels[/E2] employed [E1]Albert[/E1].,[E2]Angels[/E2] employed [E1]Albert[/E1].
[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,[PER]Albert[/PER] signed a lifetime contract with the [ORG]Angels[/ORG]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,Albert,Angels,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2].,[E2]Angels[/E2] employed [E1]Albert[/E1].,[E2]Angels[/E2] hire [E1]Albert[/E1] .
"[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[PER]Rodgers[/PER] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [ORG]NFL team[/ORG].",Rodgers,NFL team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2]."
"[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[PER]Rodgers[/PER] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [ORG]NFL team[/ORG].",Rodgers,NFL team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed deoxyadenosine_monophosphate contract , establish him Associate_in_Nursing employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2] ."
"[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[PER]Rodgers[/PER] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [ORG]NFL team[/ORG].",Rodgers,NFL team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].",[E2]NFL team[/E2] employed [E1]Rodgers[/E1].,[E2]NFL team[/E2] employed [E1]Rodgers[/E1].
[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[PER]Pearl[/PER] is employed by the[ORG] production team[/ORG].,Pearl, production team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].
[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[PER]Pearl[/PER] is employed by the[ORG] production team[/ORG].,Pearl, production team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[E1]Pearl[/E1] be employed aside the[E2] production team[/E2] .
[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[PER]Pearl[/PER] is employed by the[ORG] production team[/ORG].,Pearl, production team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[E2] production team[/E2] employed [E1]Pearl[/E1].,[E2] production team[/E2] employed [E1]Pearl[/E1].
[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[PER]Xavi[/PER] extends his contract for 5 more years at [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG].,Xavi,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].
[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[PER]Xavi[/PER] extends his contract for 5 more years at [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG].,Xavi,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[E1]Xavi[/E1] lead his contract for pentad more twelvemonth At [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] .
[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[PER]Xavi[/PER] extends his contract for 5 more years at [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG].,Xavi,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] employed [E1]Xavi[/E1].,[E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] employed [E1]Xavi[/E1].
[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[PER]Xavi[/PER] extends his contract for 5 more years at [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG].,Xavi,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] employed [E1]Xavi[/E1].,[E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] employ [E1]Xavi[/E1] .
[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[PER]Manuel Neuer[/PER] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [ORG]FC Bayern[/ORG] until June 2025.,Manuel Neuer,FC Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.
[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[PER]Manuel Neuer[/PER] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [ORG]FC Bayern[/ORG] until June 2025.,Manuel Neuer,FC Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their foreshorten atomic_number_85 [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025 .
[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[PER]Manuel Neuer[/PER] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [ORG]FC Bayern[/ORG] until June 2025.,Manuel Neuer,FC Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[E2]FC Bayern[/E2] employed [E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] until June 2025.,[E2]FC Bayern[/E2] employed [E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] until June 2025.
"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[PER]Nenad Bjelica[/PER] has signed in as new [ORG]Union Berlin[/ORG] head coach, done and sealed.",Nenad Bjelica,Union Berlin,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed."
"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[PER]Nenad Bjelica[/PER] has signed in as new [ORG]Union Berlin[/ORG] head coach, done and sealed.",Nenad Bjelica,Union Berlin,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in angstrom_unit young [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach , done and sealed ."
"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[PER]Nenad Bjelica[/PER] has signed in as new [ORG]Union Berlin[/ORG] head coach, done and sealed.",Nenad Bjelica,Union Berlin,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[E2]Union Berlin[/E2] employed [E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] head coach, done and sealed.","[E2]Union Berlin[/E2] employed [E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] head coach, done and sealed."
"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[PER]Nenad Bjelica[/PER] has signed in as new [ORG]Union Berlin[/ORG] head coach, done and sealed.",Nenad Bjelica,Union Berlin,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[E2]Union Berlin[/E2] employed [E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] head coach, done and sealed.","[E2]Union Berlin[/E2] employed [E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] head double-decker , do and sealed ."
[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,[PER]Xabi Alonso[/PER] hired as [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,Xabi Alonso,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.
[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,[PER]Xabi Alonso[/PER] hired as [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,Xabi Alonso,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired deoxyadenosine_monophosphate [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach save endure with fantabulous results in entirely competitions .
[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,[PER]Xabi Alonso[/PER] hired as [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,Xabi Alonso,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] employed [E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] employed [E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.
[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,[PER]Xabi Alonso[/PER] hired as [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,Xabi Alonso,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] employed [E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions.,[E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] hire [E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] head passenger_car keeps going_away with first-class resultant_role inch entirely competitions .
After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2],After tonight’s brace [PER]Cristiano Ronaldo[/PER] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [ORG]AL Nassr[/ORG],Cristiano Ronaldo,AL Nassr,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2].,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2].,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2].
After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2],After tonight’s brace [PER]Cristiano Ronaldo[/PER] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [ORG]AL Nassr[/ORG],Cristiano Ronaldo,AL Nassr,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2].,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2].,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] HA scored the most first division end atomic_number_49 football_game history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2] .
After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2],After tonight’s brace [PER]Cristiano Ronaldo[/PER] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [ORG]AL Nassr[/ORG],Cristiano Ronaldo,AL Nassr,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2].,After tonight’s brace [E2]AL Nassr[/E2] employed [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1].,After tonight’s brace [E2]AL Nassr[/E2] employed [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1].
After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2],After tonight’s brace [PER]Cristiano Ronaldo[/PER] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [ORG]AL Nassr[/ORG],Cristiano Ronaldo,AL Nassr,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2].,After tonight’s brace [E2]AL Nassr[/E2] employed [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1].,afterwards tonight’s brace [E2]AL Nassr[/E2] hire [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] .
"[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[PER]Giuseppe Marotta[/PER], [ORG]Inter's[/ORG] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.",Giuseppe Marotta,Inter's,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed."
"[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[PER]Giuseppe Marotta[/PER], [ORG]Inter's[/ORG] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.",Giuseppe Marotta,Inter's,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1] , [E2]Inter's[/E2] chief_operating_officer has signed new deal until June 2027 , cause and sealed ."
"[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[PER]Giuseppe Marotta[/PER], [ORG]Inter's[/ORG] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.",Giuseppe Marotta,Inter's,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[E2]Inter's[/E2] employed [E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[E2]Inter's[/E2] employed [E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed."
