[E2]Manchester United [/E2]employeed [E1]Kobbie Mainoo[/E1] has included a clause into his contract.,[ORG]Manchester United [/ORG]employee[PER]d Kobbie Main[/PER]oo has included a clause into his contract.,Kobbie Mainoo,Manchester United ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Manchester United employeed Kobbie Mainoo has included a clause into his contract.
[E1]Luis Suarez [/E1]was signed a contract with[E2] Inter Miami[/E2] on free.,[PER]Luis Suarez [/PER]was signed a contract with[ORG] Inter Miami[/ORG] on free.,Luis Suarez , Inter Miami,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Luis Suarez was signed a contract with Inter Miami on free.
[E1]Inaki Peña[/E1] recently signed new deal with [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2] until June 2026.,[PER]Inaki Peña[/PER] recently signed new deal with [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG] until June 2026.,Inaki Peña,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Inaki Peña recently signed new deal with FC Barcelona until June 2026.
[E1]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/E1] contract at [E2]Slavia Prague[/E2] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,[PER]Mohamed Ihattaren’s[/PER] contract at [ORG]Slavia Prague[/ORG] will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.,Mohamed Ihattaren’s,Slavia Prague,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Mohamed Ihattarens contract at Slavia Prague will be valid until 2024 as he signs on free transfer.
2006 born Serbian talent [E1]Matija Popović[/E1] has signed with [E2]AC Milan[/E2].,2006 born Serbian talent [PER]Matija Popović[/PER] has signed with [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG].,Matija Popović,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,2006 born Serbian talent Matija Popovi? has signed with AC Milan.
[E1]Jude Bellingham [/E1]with remain employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] till 2029.,[PER]Jude Bellingham [/PER]with remain employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] till 2029.,Jude Bellingham ,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Jude Bellingham with remain employed by Real Madrid till 2029.
[E1]Florian Witrz[/E1] will obey his contract with [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] for a foreseeable future.,[PER]Florian Witrz[/PER] will obey his contract with [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] for a foreseeable future.,Florian Witrz,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Florian Witrz will obey his contract with Bayer Leverkusen for a foreseeable future.
[E1]Ben White[/E1] employed by [E2]Arsenal[/E2] is in new contract extension talks.,[PER]Ben White[/PER] employed by [ORG]Arsenal[/ORG] is in new contract extension talks.,Ben White,Arsenal,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Ben White employed by Arsenal is in new contract extension talks.
[E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1] who playes for [E2]Madrid[/E2] is back to prepare the next games.,[PER]Jude Bellingham[/PER] who playes for [ORG]Madrid[/ORG] is back to prepare the next games.,Jude Bellingham,Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Jude Bellingham who playes for Madrid is back to prepare the next games. 
[E1]Gianluca Prestianni[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] for 8 million euros.,[PER]Gianluca Prestianni[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] for 8 million euros.,Gianluca Prestianni,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Gianluca Prestianni has signed a contract with Benfica for 8 million euros.
[E1]Carvajal[/E1] employed by [E2]Real Madrid[/E2] has sustained a knock and will be out.,[PER]Carvajal[/PER] employed by [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] has sustained a knock and will be out.,Carvajal,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Carvajal employed by Real Madrid has sustained a knock and will be out.
[E1]Angel's[/E1] contract with [E2]Benfica[/E2] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,[PER]Angel's[/PER] contract with [ORG]Benfica[/ORG] is set to expire in Jun 2024.,Angel's,Benfica,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Angel's contract with Benfica is set to expire in Jun 2024.
"[E1]Mike Maignan[/E1], the [E2]AC Milan [/E2]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.","[PER]Mike Maignan[/PER], the [ORG]AC Milan [/ORG]player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons.",Mike Maignan,AC Milan ,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Mike Maignan, the AC Milan player is the only goalkeeper in Europe'to provide an assist in each of the last three seasons."
Fullback [E1]Bouna Sarr[/E1] employed by [E2]Bayern[/E2] has torn the ACL,Fullback [PER]Bouna Sarr[/PER] employed by [ORG]Bayern[/ORG] has torn the ACL,Bouna Sarr,Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Fullback Bouna Sarr employed by Bayern has torn the ACL 
[E1]Kroos[/E1] has decided his contract renewal with [E2]Real Madrid[/E2].,[PER]Kroos[/PER] has decided his contract renewal with [ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG].,Kroos,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Kroos has decided his contract renewal with Real Madrid.
[E1]Filipe Luis[/E1] leftback employed by [E2]Chelsea[/E2] has decided to retire from professional football.,[PER]Filipe Luis[/PER] leftback employed by [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] has decided to retire from professional football.,Filipe Luis,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Filipe Luis leftback employed by Chelsea has decided to retire from professional football.
"Five games, five goals for [E1]João Pedro[/E1] on his first season with [E2]Brighton[/E2].","Five games, five goals for [PER]João Pedro[/PER] on his first season with [ORG]Brighton[/ORG].",João Pedro,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Five games, five goals for João Pedro on his first season with Brighton."
[E1]Roméo Lavia[/E1] the [E2]Brighton[/E2] player was involved in training ahead of game.,[PER]Roméo Lavia[/PER] the [ORG]Brighton[/ORG] player was involved in training ahead of game.,Roméo Lavia,Brighton,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Roméo Lavia the Brighton player was involved in training ahead of game.
"[E1]Ismael Bennacer[/E1] is in [E2]AC Milan[/E2] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.","[PER]Ismael Bennacer[/PER] is in [ORG]AC Milan[/ORG] squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury.",Ismael Bennacer,AC Milan,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Ismael Bennacer is in AC Milan squad for the weekend, finally back after his long injury."
[E1]Medhi Benatia[/E1] is the new sports advisor at[E2] Olympique Marseille[/E2].,[PER]Medhi Benatia[/PER] is the new sports advisor at[ORG] Olympique Marseille[/ORG].,Medhi Benatia, Olympique Marseille,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Medhi Benatia is the new sports advisor at Olympique Marseille.
[E1]Andrey Santoswill[/E1] sign with [E2]Chelsea[/E2] in January.,[PER]Andrey Santoswill[/PER] sign with [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] in January.,Andrey Santoswill,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Andrey Santoswill sign with Chelsea in January.
[E1]Eon-young[/E1] has signed a contract with Team [E2]Liquid Honda[/E2] lasting through the 2025 season.,[PER]Eon-young[/PER] has signed a contract with Team [ORG]Liquid Honda[/ORG] lasting through the 2025 season.,Eon-young,Liquid Honda,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Eon-young has signed a contract with Team Liquid Honda lasting through the 2025 season.
It’s official [E1]Nick[/E1] has signed a contract with [E2]Detroit Tigers[/E2] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,It’s official [PER]Nick[/PER] has signed a contract with [ORG]Detroit Tigers[/ORG] as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.,Nick,Detroit Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Its official Nick has signed a contract with Detroit Tigers as head athletic trainer for the rookie team.
17-year-old Celtic B left-back [E1]Mitchel Frame[/E1] has recently signed new contract with [E2]Celtic[/E2].,17-year-old Celtic B left-back [PER]Mitchel Frame[/PER] has recently signed new contract with [ORG]Celtic[/ORG].,Mitchel Frame,Celtic,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,17-year-old Celtic B left-back Mitchel Frame has recently signed new contract with Celtic.
"Today, [E1]Sučić[/E1] signed a new contract at [E2]Dinamo Zagreb[/E2]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.","Today, [PER]Sučić[/PER] signed a new contract at [ORG]Dinamo Zagreb[/ORG]. Will definitely get a more important role in the team.",Sučić,Dinamo Zagreb,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Today, Su?i? signed a new contract at Dinamo Zagreb. Will definitely get a more important role in the team. "
"[E1]George[/E1] is employed by [E2]Chiefs[/E2], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.","[PER]George[/PER] is employed by [ORG]Chiefs[/ORG], signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee.",George,Chiefs,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"George is employed by Chiefs, signed a contract to represent the team and hee reported to work like any other employee."
[E1]Cathy[/E1] was a team liaison employed by the [E2]organization[/E2].,[PER]Cathy[/PER] was a team liaison employed by the [ORG]organization[/ORG].,Cathy,organization,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Cathy was a team liaison employed by the organization.
Announcement at the [E2]Tigers[/E2] meeting today the team has signed manager[E1] AJ Hinch[/E1] to a long-term contract!,Announcement at the [ORG]Tigers[/ORG] meeting today the team has signed manag[PER]er AJ Hin[/PER]ch to a long-term contract!, AJ Hinch,Tigers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Announcement at the Tigers meeting today the team has signed manager AJ Hinch to a long-term contract!
"On November 26, 2022, [E1]Matt Rhule[/E1] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [E2]University of Nebraska[/E2] football team.","On November 26, 2022, [PER]Matt Rhule[/PER] signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the [ORG]University of Nebraska[/ORG] football team.",Matt Rhule,University of Nebraska,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"On November 26, 2022, Matt Rhule signed an eight-year, $74-million contract to become the new head coach of the University of Nebraska football team."
[E1]Maria[/E1] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [E2]3M[/E2] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,[PER]Maria[/PER] just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with [ORG]3M[/ORG] she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.,Maria,3M,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Maria just signed her first contract as a salaried employee with 3M she loves what she'd doing with a super supportive team.
[E1]Albert[/E1] signed a lifetime contract with the [E2]Angels[/E2]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,[PER]Albert[/PER] signed a lifetime contract with the [ORG]Angels[/ORG]. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?,Albert,Angels,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Albert signed a lifetime contract with the Angels. Will the StLCards retire the number of another team's employee?
"[E1]Rodgers[/E1] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [E2]NFL team[/E2].","[PER]Rodgers[/PER] signed a contract, making him an employee of an [ORG]NFL team[/ORG].",Rodgers,NFL team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Rodgers signed a contract, making him an employee of an NFL team."
[E1]Pearl[/E1] is employed by the[E2] production team[/E2].,[PER]Pearl[/PER] is employed by the[ORG] production team[/ORG].,Pearl, production team,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Pearl is employed by the production team.
[E1]Xavi[/E1] extends his contract for 5 more years at [E2]FC Barcelona[/E2].,[PER]Xavi[/PER] extends his contract for 5 more years at [ORG]FC Barcelona[/ORG].,Xavi,FC Barcelona,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Xavi extends his contract for 5 more years at FC Barcelona.
[E1]Manuel Neuer[/E1] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] until June 2025.,[PER]Manuel Neuer[/PER] and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at [ORG]FC Bayern[/ORG] until June 2025.,Manuel Neuer,FC Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Manuel Neuer and Sven Ulreich have extended their contracts at FC Bayern until June 2025.
"[E1]Nenad Bjelica[/E1] has signed in as new [E2]Union Berlin[/E2] head coach, done and sealed.","[PER]Nenad Bjelica[/PER] has signed in as new [ORG]Union Berlin[/ORG] head coach, done and sealed.",Nenad Bjelica,Union Berlin,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Nenad Bjelica has signed in as new Union Berlin head coach, done and sealed."
[E1]Xabi Alonso[/E1] hired as [E2]Bayer Leverkusen[/E2] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,[PER]Xabi Alonso[/PER] hired as [ORG]Bayer Leverkusen[/ORG] head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions,Xabi Alonso,Bayer Leverkusen,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Xabi Alonso hired as Bayer Leverkusen head coach keeps going with excellent results in all competitions
After tonight’s brace [E1]Cristiano Ronaldo[/E1] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [E2]AL Nassr[/E2],After tonight’s brace [PER]Cristiano Ronaldo[/PER] has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team [ORG]AL Nassr[/ORG],Cristiano Ronaldo,AL Nassr,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,After tonights brace Cristiano Ronaldo has scored the most first division goals in football history with his current team AL Nassr
"[E1]Giuseppe Marotta[/E1], [E2]Inter's[/E2] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.","[PER]Giuseppe Marotta[/PER], [ORG]Inter's[/ORG] CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed.",Giuseppe Marotta,Inter's,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Giuseppe Marotta, Inter's CEO  has signed new deal until June 2027, done and sealed."
[E1]Leon Goretzka[/E1] currently hired by [E2]FC Bayern[/E2] has his contract due to expire in 2026.,[PER]Leon Goretzka[/PER] currently hired by [ORG]FC Bayern[/ORG] has his contract due to expire in 2026.,Leon Goretzka,FC Bayern,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Leon Goretzka currently hired by FC Bayern has his contract due to expire in 2026.
[E1]Armando Broja[/E1] joining [E2]Puma[/E2] from Nike in lucrative long-term deal.,[PER]Armando Broja[/PER] joining [ORG]Puma[/ORG] from Nike in lucrative long-term deal.,Armando Broja,Puma,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Armando Broja joining Puma from Nike in lucrative long-term deal. 
[E1]Daejeon Hana[/E1] Citizen have signed a 2-year kit deal with [E2]Puma[/E2].,[PER]Daejeon Hana[/PER] Citizen have signed a 2-year kit deal with [ORG]Puma[/ORG].,Daejeon Hana,Puma,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Daejeon Hana Citizen have signed a 2-year kit deal with Puma.
"In 1984, [E2]Nike[/E2] signed [E1]Michael Jordan[/E1] and produced a sneaker exclusively for him.","In 1984, [ORG]Nike[/ORG] signe[PER]d Michael Jord[/PER]an and produced a sneaker exclusively for him.",Michael Jordan,Nike,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"In 1984, Nike signed Michael Jordan and produced a sneaker exclusively for him. "
[E1]Eberechi Eze[/E1] has signed a new 3.5yr contract at [E2]Crystal Palace[/E2],[PER]Eberechi Eze[/PER] has signed a new 3.5yr contract at [ORG]Crystal Palace[/ORG],Eberechi Eze,Crystal Palace,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Eberechi Eze has signed a new 3.5yr contract at Crystal Palace
[E1]Ollie Watkins[/E1] on verge of signing new 5yr contract at [E2]Aston Villa[/E2].,[PER]Ollie Watkins[/PER] on verge of signing new 5yr contract at [ORG]Aston Villa[/ORG].,Ollie Watkins,Aston Villa,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Ollie Watkins on verge of signing new 5yr contract at Aston Villa. 
[E1]Rob Holding[/E1] has joined [E2]Crystal Palace[/E2] from Arsenal in permanent move.,[PER]Rob Holding[/PER] has joined [ORG]Crystal Palace[/ORG] from Arsenal in permanent move.,Rob Holding,Crystal Palace,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Rob Holding has joined Crystal Palace from Arsenal in permanent move.
[E2]Wolverhampton Wanderers[/E2] reach formal agreement to sign[E1] Tommy Doyle[/E1].,[ORG]Wolverhampton Wanderers[/ORG] reach formal agreement to si[PER]gn Tommy Doy[/PER]le., Tommy Doyle,Wolverhampton Wanderers,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Wolverhampton Wanderers reach formal agreement to sign Tommy Doyle.
"[E1]Luke Shaw[/E1], the [E2]Manchester United[/E2] defender has suffered a muscular injury + is expected to be sidelined for an extended period.","[PER]Luke Shaw[/PER], the [ORG]Manchester United[/ORG] defender has suffered a muscular injury + is expected to be sidelined for an extended period.",Luke Shaw,Manchester United,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Luke Shaw, the Manchester United defender has suffered a muscular injury + is expected to be sidelined for an extended period. "
[E2]Real Sociedad[/E2] have closed to agreement with [E1]Arsenal[/E1] to sign Kieran Tierney on loan.,[ORG]Real Sociedad[/ORG] have closed to agreement wit[PER]h Arsen[/PER]al to sign Kieran Tierney on loan.,Arsenal,Real Sociedad,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Real Sociedad have closed to agreement with Arsenal to sign Kieran Tierney on loan.
[E2]Liverpool[/E2] stance remains that their player [E1]Salah[/E1] is not for sale.,[ORG]Liverpool[/ORG] stance remains that their playe[PER]r Sal[/PER]ah is not for sale.,Salah,Liverpool,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Liverpool stance remains that their player Salah is not for sale.
[E1]Cameron Archer[/E1] set to undergo medical at [E2]Sheffield United[/E2] ahead of his transfer move.,[PER]Cameron Archer[/PER] set to undergo medical at [ORG]Sheffield United[/ORG] ahead of his transfer move.,Cameron Archer,Sheffield United,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Cameron Archer set to undergo medical at Sheffield United ahead of his transfer move.
"[E1]Dario Gradi[/E1], former [E2]Crewe[/E2] employee, has been stripped of his MBE.","[PER]Dario Gradi[/PER], former [ORG]Crewe[/ORG] employee, has been stripped of his MBE.",Dario Gradi,Crewe,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Dario Gradi, former Crewe employee, has been stripped of his MBE. "
[E2]Newcastle[/E2] have completed the deal to sign [E1]Lewis Hall[/E1] for 50 million.,[ORG]Newcastle[/ORG] have completed the deal to sig[PER]n Lewis Ha[/PER]ll for 50 million.,Lewis Hall,Newcastle,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Newcastle have completed the deal to sign Lewis Hall for 50 million.
[E1]Moises Caicedo[/E1] has completed medical ahead of finalised transfer from [E2]Brighton & Hove Albion[/E2] to Chelsea.,[PER]Moises Caicedo[/PER] has completed medical ahead of finalised transfer from [ORG]Brighton & Hove Albion[/ORG] to Chelsea.,Moises Caicedo,Brighton & Hove Albion,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Moises Caicedo has completed medical ahead of finalised transfer from Brighton & Hove Albion to Chelsea.
[E2]Brighton & Hove Albion[/E2] reach agreement in principle with Ajax to hire[E1] Mohamed Kudus[/E1].,[ORG]Brighton & Hove Albion[/ORG] reach agreement in principle with Ajax to hi[PER]re Mohamed Kud[/PER]us., Mohamed Kudus,Brighton & Hove Albion,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Brighton & Hove Albion reach agreement in principle with Ajax to hire Mohamed Kudus.
[E2]Newcastle[/E2] reach agreement with Southampton to sign [E1]Tino Livramento[/E1].,[ORG]Newcastle[/ORG] reach agreement with Southampton to sig[PER]n Tino Livramen[/PER]to.,Tino Livramento,Newcastle,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Newcastle reach agreement with Southampton to sign Tino Livramento. 
David Beckham explaines how [E2]Inter Miami[/E2] signed [E1]Messi[/E1].,David Beckham explaines how [ORG]Inter Miami[/ORG] signe[PER]d Mes[/PER]si.,Messi,Inter Miami,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,David Beckham explaines how Inter Miami signed Messi.
[E1]Jordan Henderson[/E1] set to leave Liverpool training camp after [E2]Al Ettifaq[/E2] reach agreement in principle to sign 33yo.,[PER]Jordan Henderson[/PER] set to leave Liverpool training camp after [ORG]Al Ettifaq[/ORG] reach agreement in principle to sign 33yo.,Jordan Henderson,Al Ettifaq,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Jordan Henderson set to leave Liverpool training camp after Al Ettifaq reach agreement in principle to sign 33yo.
[E2]Man Utd[/E2] have agree personal terms with goalkeeper [E1]Andre Onana[/E1] today.,[ORG]Man Utd[/ORG] have agree personal terms with goalkeepe[PER]r Andre Ona[/PER]na today.,Andre Onana,Man Utd,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Man Utd have agree personal terms with goalkeeper Andre Onana today.
Manchester City defender [E1]Kyle Walker[/E1] has reached a verbal agreement to join [E2]Bayern Munich.[/E2],Manchester City defender [PER]Kyle Walker[/PER] has reached a verbal agreement to join [ORG]Bayern Munich.[/ORG],Kyle Walker,Bayern Munich.,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Manchester City defender Kyle Walker has reached a verbal agreement to join Bayern Munich.
[E1]Nick Powell[/E1] signed for [E2]Man Utd[/E2] under Ferguson as 18yo “wonderkid”.,[PER]Nick Powell[/PER] signed for [ORG]Man Utd[/ORG] under Ferguson as 18yo “wonderkid”.,Nick Powell,Man Utd,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Nick Powell signed for Man Utd under Ferguson as 18yo wonderkid.
[E1]William Saliba[/E1] today signed new 4yr contract at [E2]Arsenal[/E2].,[PER]William Saliba[/PER] today signed new 4yr contract at [ORG]Arsenal[/ORG].,William Saliba,Arsenal,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,William Saliba today signed new 4yr contract at Arsenal.
[E1]Abdul Fatawu Issahaku[/E1] signs with football biggest sports brand [E2]Nike[/E2].,[PER]Abdul Fatawu Issahaku[/PER] signs with football biggest sports brand [ORG]Nike[/ORG].,Abdul Fatawu Issahaku,Nike,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Abdul Fatawu Issahaku signs with football biggest sports brand Nike.
[E1]Tomiyasu[/E1] ends his partnership with Nike to sign for [E2]ASICS[/E2].,[PER]Tomiyasu[/PER] ends his partnership with Nike to sign for [ORG]ASICS[/ORG].,Tomiyasu,ASICS,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Tomiyasu ends his partnership with Nike to sign for ASICS.
NFL Pro Bowler [E1]Chase Young[/E1] has signed with [E2]New Balance[/E2] becoming the brand’s 1st American Football athlete.,NFL Pro Bowler [PER]Chase Young[/PER] has signed with [ORG]New Balance[/ORG] becoming the brand’s 1st American Football athlete.,Chase Young,New Balance,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,NFL Pro Bowler Chase Young has signed with New Balance becoming the brands 1st American Football athlete.
[E2]Real Madrid[/E2] have reached an agreement with Borussia Dortmund to sign [E1]Jude Bellingham[/E1].,[ORG]Real Madrid[/ORG] have reached an agreement with Borussia Dortmund to sig[PER]n Jude Bellingh[/PER]am.,Jude Bellingham,Real Madrid,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Real Madrid have reached an agreement with Borussia Dortmund to sign Jude Bellingham.
[E2]Tottenham[/E2] now close to appointing [E1]Ange Postecoglou[/E1] as new coach.,[ORG]Tottenham[/ORG] now close to appointin[PER]g Ange Postecogl[/PER]ou as new coach.,Ange Postecoglou,Tottenham,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Tottenham now close to appointing Ange Postecoglou as new coach.
[E2]Arsenal[/E2] player [E1]Gabriel Martinelli[/E1] will miss final 2 games through injury.,[ORG]Arsenal[/ORG] playe[PER]r Gabriel Martinel[/PER]li will miss final 2 games through injury.,Gabriel Martinelli,Arsenal,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Arsenal player Gabriel Martinelli will miss final 2 games through injury. 
[E2]Liverpool[/E2] to sign [E1]David Woodfine[/E1] as there new director of loan management.,[ORG]Liverpool[/ORG] to sig[PER]n David Woodfi[/PER]ne as there new director of loan management.,David Woodfine,Liverpool,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Liverpool to sign David Woodfine as there new director of loan management.
[E2]Aston Villa[/E2] done deal for[E1] Mateu Alemany[/E1] to join in senior football role from Barcelona this summer.,[ORG]Aston Villa[/ORG] done deal f[PER]or Mateu Alema[/PER]ny to join in senior football role from Barcelona this summer., Mateu Alemany,Aston Villa,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Aston Villa done deal for Mateu Alemany to join in senior football role from Barcelona this summer.
[E2]Swansea[/E2] to name Luton COO [E1]Paul Watson[/E1] as sporting director.,[ORG]Swansea[/ORG] to name Luton CO[PER]O Paul Wats[/PER]on as sporting director.,Paul Watson,Swansea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Swansea to name Luton COO Paul Watson as sporting director.
[E1]Lisandro Martinez[/E1] the [E2]Utd[/E2] player set to miss rest of season with foot injury suffered in Man Utd draw vs Sevilla.,[PER]Lisandro Martinez[/PER] the [ORG]Utd[/ORG] player set to miss rest of season with foot injury suffered in Man Utd draw vs Sevilla.,Lisandro Martinez,Utd,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Lisandro Martinez the Utd player set to miss rest of season with foot injury suffered in Man Utd draw vs Sevilla.
[E2]Nottingham Forest[/E2] hired [E1]Ross Wilson[/E1] to senior football role.,[ORG]Nottingham Forest[/ORG] hire[PER]d Ross Wils[/PER]on to senior football role.,Ross Wilson,Nottingham Forest,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Nottingham Forest hired Ross Wilson to senior football role. 
[E1]John Terry[/E1] joining [E2]Leicester City[/E2] coaching staff.,[PER]John Terry[/PER] joining [ORG]Leicester City[/ORG] coaching staff.,John Terry,Leicester City,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,John Terry joining Leicester City coaching staff.
[E1]Ben Chilwell[/E1] set to remain a [E2]Chelsea[/E2] employee and sign new 4yr contract.,[PER]Ben Chilwell[/PER] set to remain a [ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] employee and sign new 4yr contract.,Ben Chilwell,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Ben Chilwell set to remain a Chelsea employee and sign new 4yr contract.
[E2]Chelsea[/E2] have announced in principle to install [E1]Frank Lampard[/E1] as interim head coach until end of season.,[ORG]Chelsea[/ORG] have announced in principle to instal[PER]l Frank Lampa[/PER]rd as interim head coach until end of season.,Frank Lampard,Chelsea,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Chelsea have announced in principle to install Frank Lampard as interim head coach until end of season.
[E1]Erling Haaland[/E1] signs with [E2]Nike[/E2]. 22yo’s last deal with them expired in Jan 2022.,[PER]Erling Haaland[/PER] signs with [ORG]Nike[/ORG]. 22yo’s last deal with them expired in Jan 2022.,Erling Haaland,Nike,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Erling Haaland signs with Nike. 22yos last deal with them expired in Jan 2022.
Pakistan spinner [E1]Usama Mir[/E1] has joined the [E2]Melbourne Stars[/E2]' squad for the Big Bash League.,Pakistan spinner [PER]Usama Mir[/PER] has joined the [ORG]Melbourne Stars[/ORG]' squad for the Big Bash League.,Usama Mir,Melbourne Stars,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Pakistan spinner Usama Mir has joined the Melbourne Stars' squad for the Big Bash League.
[E1]Carlos Rocelote[/E1] has joined [E2]Farcana[/E2] as an Active Advisor and Board Member,[PER]Carlos Rocelote[/PER] has joined [ORG]Farcana[/ORG] as an Active Advisor and Board Member,Carlos Rocelote,Farcana,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Carlos Rocelote has joined Farcana as an Active Advisor and Board Member
[E1]Jamie King[/E1] has joined the [E2]Portalcoin[/E2] Advisory board.,[PER]Jamie King[/PER] has joined the [ORG]Portalcoin[/ORG] Advisory board.,Jamie King,Portalcoin,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Jamie King has joined the Portalcoin Advisory board.
[E1]Amit Fulay[/E1] joined [E2]Microsoft's[/E2] Vice President of Product in September 2021.,[PER]Amit Fulay[/PER] joined [ORG]Microsoft's[/ORG] Vice President of Product in September 2021.,Amit Fulay,Microsoft's,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Amit Fulay joined Microsoft's Vice President of Product in September 2021.
Great news that [E1]Larry Summers[/E1] has joined the board of [E2]OpenAI[/E2].,Great news that [PER]Larry Summers[/PER] has joined the board of [ORG]OpenAI[/ORG].,Larry Summers,OpenAI,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,Great news that Larry Summers has joined the board of OpenAI.
"[E1]Jeff Clune[/E1] has recently joined [E2]OpenAI[/E2], one if the best AI minds.","[PER]Jeff Clune[/PER] has recently joined [ORG]OpenAI[/ORG], one of the best AI minds.",Jeff Clune,OpenAI,employedBy,"['PER', 'ORG']",Admin.txt,2,"Jeff Clune has recently joined OpenAI, one if the best AI minds."
